{"data":[{"question":"What did you think of the politician's speech? \"He _________ for half an hour and indeed _________ something.\"","a":"spoke, speak","b":"spoke, say","c":"said, speak","d":"said, say","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Speak: is to say words out loud, the act of speech; \n- Say: is to speak to someone","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"I can hardly hear the music. Would you please ___?","a":"turn it down","b":"turn it on","c":"turn it off","d":"turn it up","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Turn up: to turn a switch on a machine such as an oven, radio etc so that it produces more heat, sound etc","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"I love to go to the beach in summer. It ___ great to lie in the sun or swim in the cool sea.","a":"feels","b":"does","c":"makes","d":"gets","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Feel: experience a particular physical feeling or emotion","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Julia _________ Steven's number in the phone book to make sure that she had got it right.","a":"looked for","b":"looked up","c":"picked up","d":"picked out","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Pick out: to choose someone or something from a group","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Nobody noticed that there was a thief slipping into the house because the lights happened to ___.","a":"give in","b":"be put up","c":"go out","d":"be turned on","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Go out: to stop burning or shining","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"The captain ___ an apology to the passengers for the unexpected delay.","a":"said","b":"made","c":"passed","d":"put","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Make an apology for sth: feel sorry for what happen","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Rather than _________ on a crowded bus, Jimmy always prefers ___ a motorcycle.","a":"riding, ride","b":"ride, ride","c":"to ride, riding","d":"ride, to ride","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Rather than + infinitve without to\n- Prefer + To Verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"I don't know the movie theater, but it's ___ to be quite a bad one.","a":"told","b":"said","c":"talked","d":"spoken","answer":"2","explain":"\n- They say\/people say\/ it is said (that): used to talk about something that people think is true","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"All the leading newspapers ___ the trade talks among the APEC member countries.","a":"printed","b":"reported","c":"published","d":"announced","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Report: to tell someone about what has been happening, or what you are doing as part of your job","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"You are ___ your time trying to persuade the old man; he'll never join us.","a":"wasting","b":"spending","c":"missing","d":"losing","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Wash your time\/money: to use more money, time, energy etc than is useful or sensible","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"}]}